planned but welcome back to the channel
this time to talk about building people
hopeful for
williams-sonoma scripta
industries of tokyo
you can run industry and common law and
home industry and potential parishioners
from its use for our newspaper consumers
quite strong
rigidly budget instrument brown proved
miners d
um... the uh... the name of the script
and on the parameters
whatsoever
rendell's included both
if some kind of uh... what images you
all
trains out of the first line in middle
school to the next time that uh... is
supposed to be executed
and then the provides news approach
direction type in the various commands
to the people
first and most important
is the pw
dozens of little street veggie burger
so eric peers and want to get rid of it
press
q enter and referred
that's right again
the second most important
which is page
providing us this help
so you can see here there is optional
specifically the shortlist
ought to be by the recipient
and know that there are polls of
potential and
possible ways to use in the world
area in order to see now that uh... the
code again
personnel
which is that provides a listing of the
cold
and in the south
and assisting you will see the light
numbers
so discouraged points to mine
that isn't next line to be executed so
that's why it hasn't been easy thing to
do that
if i want to see what's been the boiler
file variable
image it
is supposed to be empty actually
i can use that
ritual expense for print dander
provide the name of the revel
over the spring
game actually acted even checked later
is defined or more
i can write it he defined and it flows
return
it folds
uh...
strydom convincing
if i did was trying to do something more
complex equipment
is modified into a print out some kind
of inside you
but i think i did
uh... let's see while can execute and
uh... this lying still
i would like to get back to this point
and execute this line of code
had to do that process which means step
for stepping in
and customs
that execute that line of code and
solely the next
line to be executed
the fact that i would think of the
content to file
then you will see that is already have
that valujet was
provided commonplace
plus i have cancer
at least information
and i know that i would like to call the
next uh... live
let's let's talk in the summer
which is coming from module
pressing guess again
execute
over the next day
piece of school
rejection according to that recording
that
if function
so what you see here instead decided of
printed out first
line
to be executed invest under fire
so you can see that
this is the name of that
package
and father who is
reach father is the name of the
functioned as being cold which is a bit
strange because the cold and uh...
function at schools lar
and instead of death
your own
refund and have to see what's
going longer and this is the name of the
file
an actual implementation of the retrial
and in the area of low interest and five
so this is an eleven x
line to be executed
let's look around so let's play l
original flight numbers
seventy to eighty
and to show us the lines
and uh...
fahnestock
in between those lines and here you can
see that the iraqi yes we are in the
meantime
fanciful stalled
above it
you see that actually miss their
function is in eighty s refile function
so that experienced while the new york
calling so
sexually
a guessing all seem to be thoughtful
shin
no injuries far function
edge
this is the next is that to be executed
if i want to do an executed
i can press s again
but it's not necessary actually because
if i just friends
pressed enter the two countries say that
executes the scene
as someone that was given earlier
this way i can just print press enter
all the time and see the groom
step-by-step
and uncalled for
old values
or that uh... status that article
operable you might thing that all this
is not the function of your actually
want to give up
wanted to get
ordered function
expecting the destruction into sort
function but you don't really care
because you already know that the book
problem whatever you're looking for is
not clear
so you would like to return from the
function
without stepping
those who hold a
allowance one-by-one forty histories
that far
before doing that actually
let's do something else
let's see the two nd which provides its
best extremes
so what i pressed team i concede
what there i am
in the cooled and you can see that this
is the only cooled
that has been made so there's only one
if function in tuesday
personnel are
in return from the current from churches
to function
answering of their return values and
this time because the return value
is the content both the padre pio polla
you see that through the content of the
file
which is just a end of the p_l_o_
follows the completes the documentation
families do not need list of the names
who contributed to the culture project
and by the retake control of them
so we go back to the code
assira you can see the line the next
line
is should be executed
and uh... which is a cold
eddie totals are planned new ones and
the fine
function
formato
so that's precisely can't and step ended
up in the book
let's look around
former forty five to c sixty
you see your
probably deserves and realize that there
will be straight here
and then we are into finding a new
methods being spent on the first line of
tonight and
the step
and uh... at this time
and it is sad that we don't care about
the process of so don't want to spend in
previously
stepped into the store function and then
he'll be drawn and found out that we
don't care about is overstepped ultimate
using pyar
in this time i can use that then
which means next step
and it represents are on this
recordable photos dot from the executed
but today by the the government's
at that point
just offer
the the
that's what friendship calls are next
line fifty st
here at the top you can see that this is
next
allied to be executed
and here in the area
now we can present to regain
and an interview
fighter escort and so i understand
enforcement
the generals must sing reviewed earlier
safe represent
answer now
it's a step over the cool
through the p_p_i_
and um...
i think that's that's a formal probably
old confirmable
tutorial about that
just don't forget that using q allow you
to exit do judy parker
if you're interested to problem too
the darker there's an excellent book let
me show you this this one
uh... by a refund to buy this book and
and reviewed
do commitment i didn't write it
uh... but uh... you can learn quite a
lot for it
so thank you for watching than that
please come back later on